inseego.com 2019-03-21

# Privacy Policy | Inseego Corp

**Introduction**

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) provides information about how Inseego, Inc. (“we”) collects and uses data which is personally identifiable. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the personal information that you share with us.

**Scope**

When you register for various services offered on our website, personal information is collected as actively submitted data. Personal information includes a login name and password, your first and last name, your email address and any other personal contact information provided to us by you. We do not automatically collect your personal information. We do collect data such as the internet address of your computer (“IP address”), the amount of time spent at any particular domain on our website and visitor activity.

**How We Use Information Collected**

Inseego uses all data collected to fulfill your requests for certain products, services and software updates, and potentially in the future, to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, special offers or other information we think you’d like to be informed about (either from us or from our business partners). We might use your information to send you direct marketing information or contact you for market research.

**Internal Information Sharing**

Inseego is a global company, therefore your personal information might be shared with other worldwide Inseego offices and subsidiaries, all of which are governed by this Privacy Policy or are bound by confidentiality and data transfer agreements.

**Maintaining Account Information**

Registered Inseego account users may request to update or delete account information held, by sending an email to webmaster@inseego.us.

**Data Privacy and Security**

Your Inseego account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. We safeguard the security of the information you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. Industry-standard SSL-encryption (128 bit secure socket layer) firewalls are used in areas of our website, in addition to security systems which enhance secure data transmissions. Your personal information is what we aim to protect, however, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Always make sure you use a secure browser and change your password from time to time.

**Children’s Privacy**

The site is intended for persons over the age of 13. We do not target or solicit, nor do we intentionally or knowingly collect, information which is personal and identifiable from children under the age of 13.

**Effective Date, Amendments**

This Policy is effective as of December 9, 2009. We reserve the right to update this Policy at any time without notice to you. When you visit our website, you accept the current version of this Policy as posted at that time.

**Contact Us**

Please feel free to contact us regarding this Policy. You may send us an email at webmaster@nvtl.com or write to us at Inseego, Inc., Attention: Legal Department, 9605 Scranton Road, Ste 300, San Diego, CA 92121.
